Guide to the Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files, 1949-1979
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series V. Within the College, 1951-1979
  - Student Interns — Vassar, 1968-1969 (Folder 53.39)
  - Student Intern (foreign), 1968-1969 (Folder 53.40)
  - SDS — Students for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Folder 53.41)
  - Student Unrest, 1968-1969 (Folder 53.42)
  - Student Unrest, 1968-1969 (Folder 54.1)
  - Student Unrest, 1968 (Folder 54.2)
  - Summer Use of the Campus, 1968-1969 (Folder 54.3)
  - Summer Institute — Geology, 1968-1969 (Folder 54.4)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1968 (Folder 54.5)
  - Tuition, 1967-1968 (Folder 54.6)
  - Student Sponsored Seminar on urban Issues, 1968-1969 (Folder 54.7)
  - Vassar College Summer Program, 1969 (Folder 54.8)
  - Summer Program for Disadvantaged Residents in Poughkeepsie Area, 1968-1969 (Folder 54.9)
  - Vassar Summer Internship Program in Washington, 1969 (Folder 54.10)
  - Sub Rosa, 1968-1969 (Folder 54.11)
  - Administrative Staff, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.12)
  - Airline Travel, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.13)
  - Assistant to the President, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.14)
  - Auditors, 1969 (Folder 54.15)
  - Urban Center for Black Studies, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.16)
  - Black Studies Program, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.17)
  - Black Studies, 1969 (Folder 54.18)
  - Black Housing, 1970 Apr (Folder 54.19)
  - Black Students — Housing, 1970 (Folder 54.20)
  - Black Studies Program, 1969-1970; (3 folders) (Folder 54.21)
  - Black Studies, 1969 (Folder 54.22)
  - Black Studies, 1969 (Folder 54.23)
  - Black Studies, Fall 1969 (Folder 54.24)
  - Black Studies — Vassar Review, 1969 (Folder 54.25)
  - Black Studies Committee, 1970 (Folder 54.26)
  - Black Students Sit-In, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.27)
  - Black Student Sit-In — Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.28)
  - Black Sit-In, 1969 (Folder 54.29)
  - Black Applicants for Positions, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.30)
  - Black Housing, 1970 (Folder 54.31)
  - Sarah Gibson Blanding, 1969-1970 (Folder 54.32)
  - Blood Bank, 1970 (Folder 54.33)
  - Central Administration, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.1)
  - Amendment of Charter, 1968-1969 (Folder 55.2)
  - Chauffeur Service, 1969 (Folder 55.3)
  - Chicago Hall, 1969 (Folder 55.4)
  - Clippings, 1968-1970 (Folder 55.5)
  - Coed Living, 1969 (Folder 55.6)
  - College Assembly, 1969-1970; (empty) (Folder 55.7)
  - College Council, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.8)
  - College Government Association, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.9)
  - College Research Center, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.10)
  - Criteria for Promotion and Tenure, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.11)
  - Computer Center, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.12)
  - Critical Language Program, 1969 (Folder 55.13)
  - Dictaphone, 1965 (Folder 55.14)
  - Drugs on Campus, 1969 (Folder 55.15)
  - East Asian Studies, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.16)
  - Entertainment at President’s House, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.17)
  - Environmental Studies, 1968-1969 (Folder 55.18)
  - Exchange and Transfer Program (with other institutions), 1967-1969 (Folder 55.19)
  - Exchange and Transfer Students (with other institutions), 1968-1969 (Folder 55.20)
  - Exchange and Transfer Students, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.21)
  - Vassar College Exchange Program, Spring 1969 (Folder 55.22)
  - Exchange and Transfer Program, 1968-1970 (Folder 55.23)
  - Faculty Chairs, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.24)
  - Faculty Children Tuition, 1969-1970; (empty) (Folder 55.25)
  - Foreign Students, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.26)
  - Form Letters, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.27)
  - Founders Day, 1969-1970; (empty) (Folder 55.28)
  - From Vassar, 1969-1970; (empty) (Folder 55.29)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Teaching (Candidates), 1967-1968 (Folder 55.30)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Teaching, 1968 (Folder 55.31)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Teaching, 1969 (Folder 55.32)
  - Frankel Institute, 1968 (Folder 55.33)
  - Frankel (Folder 55.34)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Teaching, 1969 (Folder 55.35)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Teaching (Mr. Frankel), 1969 (Folder 55.36)
  - U.S. India Women’s College Program, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.37)
  - Junior Year Abroad, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.38)
  - Jury Duty, 1961-1969 (Folder 55.39)
  - La Napoule, 1967-1969 (Folder 55.40)
  - Henry Noble MacCracken, 1970-1974 (Folder 55.41)
  - Mathew Club, 1970 (Folder 55.42)
  - Memorial Minutes, 1969 (Folder 55.43)
  - Parietals, 1969 (Folder 55.44)
  - Petitions, 1970 (Folder 55.45)
  - Postponed Minnewaska Conference III, 1970 Apr (Folder 55.46)
  - Minnewaska Conference III, 1969 Oct-Nov (Folder 55.47)
  - Miscellany News, 1969-1970 (Folder 55.48)
  - Off Campus Studies, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.1)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.2)
  - Office of Public Relations, Administrative Director — M. Gilbert, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.3)
  - Public Relations — News Office, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.4)
  - Office of Public Relations — News Releases, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.5)
  - Publications, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.6)
  - Questionnaires, 1969 (Folder 56.7)
  - Questionnaires (Unanswered), 1969-1970 (Folder 56.8)
  - Registration — 1970, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.9)
  - The River Course, 1969 (Folder 56.10)
  - Salary Scale, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.11)
  - Mr. Simpson’s Notes to Himself, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.12)
  - Letters to Mr. Simpson (from Velma), 1969-1970 (Folder 56.13)
  - Social Regulations, 1969-1970; (empty) (Folder 56.14)
  - Sophomore Fathers Weekend, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.15)
  - Station Wagon, 1966 (Folder 56.16)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1969 (Folder 56.17)
  - Student Interns — Vassar ’69-70, 1969 (Folder 56.18)
  - Sub Rosa, 1969-1970; (empty) (Folder 56.19)
  - Suffrage (Academic), 1966-1969 (Folder 56.20)
  - Summer Program for Disadvantaged Residents in Poughkeepsie Area, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.21)
  - Summer Session Inquiries re: (General), 1969 (Folder 56.22)
  - Summer Institute — Geology, 1969 (Folder 56.23)
  - Student Unrest, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.24)
  - Tax Reform Bill, 1969 (Folder 56.25)
  - Tuition, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.26)
  - Urban Studies, 1969 (Folder 56.27)
  - Vietnam Moratorium, 1969 (Folder 56.28)
  - Women’s Liberation Movement, 1970 (Folder 56.29)
  - Administrative Staff, 1970 (Folder 56.30)
  - Assistant to President, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.31)
  - Auditors, 1970 (Folder 56.32)
  - Black Studies Program, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.33)
  - Black Studies Appointments, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.34)
  - Black Housing, 1971 (Folder 56.35)
  - Black Applicants for Positions, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.36)
  - Sarah Gibson Blanding, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.37)
  - Blood bank, 1971 (Folder 56.38)
  - Central Administration, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.39)
  - Clippings, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.40)
  - Coeducation: Second Thoughts, 1971 (Folder 56.41)
  - College Council, 1970 (Folder 56.42)
  - College Research Center, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.43)
  - Computer Center, 1971 (Folder 56.44)
  - Drugs on Campus, 1970 (Folder 56.45)
  - East Asian Studies, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.46)
  - Entertainment at President’s House, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.47)
  - Environmental Studies, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.48)
  - Faculty: Criteria for Promotion and Tenure, (empty) (Folder 56.49)
  - Faculty: hiring and Review, 1971 (Folder 56.50)
  - Faculty and Course Evaluation, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.51)
  - Faculty: Tenure Regulations, 1971 (Folder 56.52)
  - Foreign Students, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.53)
  - Form Letters, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.54)
  - U.S. India Women’s College Program, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.55)
  - Junior Year Abroad, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.56)
  - Leaves of Absence, 1971 (Folder 56.57)
  - Minnewaska Conference, 1970 (Folder 56.58)
  - Miscellany News, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.59)
  - State of the Onion, 1971 (Folder 56.60)
  - Multidisciplinary — Man and His Environment, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.61)
  - Multidisciplinary Program — Critical Thought, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.62)
  - Off Campus Studies, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.63)
  - Questionnaires, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.64)
  - President’s Report, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.65)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.66)
  - Procedures, 1969 (Folder 56.67)
  - Office of Public Relations Administrative Director — Mary Gilbert, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.68)
  - Public Relations — News Office, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.69)
  - Office of Public Relations — News Releases, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.70)
  - Publications, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.71)
  - Questionnaires — Unanswered, 1971 (Folder 56.72)
  - Registration — 1971, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.73)
  - Research Assistants employed on grants from NSF, Public Health Service, etc., 1969-1970 (Folder 56.74)
  - Salary Scale, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.75)
  - Salary Data, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.76)
  - Faculty Salary Budget 1971-1972 — VG’s Working Papers, 1970-1971 (Folder 56.77)
  - Faculty Salary Budget 1970-1971 — Working Papers, 1969-1970 (Folder 56.78)
  - Faculty Salary Budget 1970-1971 — Working Papers, 1969-1970 (Folder 57.1)
  - Faculty Salary Budget 1970-1971 — Working Paper, 1969-1970 (Folder 57.2)
  - Mr. Simpson’s Notes to Himself, 1970-1971 (Folder 57.3)
  - Sophomore Fathers Weekend, 1971 (Folder 57.4)
  - Student Government Association, 1970-1971 (Folder 57.5)
  - Judicial Board — Student Disciplinary Cases, 1971 (Folder 57.6)
  - Students — Exchange and Transfer, 1970-1971 (Folder 57.7)
  - Student Interns, 1970-1971 (Folder 57.8)
  - Faculty: Student Evaluation of Teaching, 1971 (Folder 57.9)
  - Student Sit-In re Faculty Firings — Appeals of Court Decisions, 1971 (Folder 57.10)
  - Student Sit-In, 1971 Apr (Folder 57.1)
  - Student “Strike” — Miscellaneous, 1970 May (Folder 57.12)
  - Student “Strike” Correspondence, 1970 (Folder 57.13)
  - College Court Decisions (Sit-In), 1971 May (Folder 57.14)
  - Mary Grayson Appeal of College Court Decisions in re Student Sit-In, 1971 (Folder 57.15)
  - Student Sit-In — Faculty Terminations, 1971 (Folder 57.16)
  - Faculty Firing (Sit-In), 1971 (Folder 57.17)
  - Student Unrest, 1970 (Folder 57.18)
  - Fall Recess (Campaigning for Candidates), 1970 (Folder 57.19)
  - Washington Summer Intern Program, 1969-1970 (Folder 57.20)
  - Telephone Numbers (seldom used), 1968-1969 (Folder 57.21)
  - Tuition, 1970 (Folder 57.22)
  - Women’s Liberation Movement, 1970-1971 (Folder 57.23)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1971-1972 (Folder 57.24)
  - African Field Trip, 1970-1971 (Folder 57.25)
  - Academic Freedom, 1971 (Folder 57.26)
  - American Culture, 1971-1973 (Folder 57.27)
  - Asian Studies, 1970-1972 (Folder 57.28)
  - Assistant to the president, 1971-1972 (Folder 57.29)
  - Assistant to the President (Mrs. Havelock), 1971-1973 (Folder 57.30)
  - Black Affairs — Chronological Files, 1969-1972 (Folder 58.1)
  - Assistant to the President for Black Affairs, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.2)
  - Black Housing — Kendrick House, 1973 (Folder 58.3)
  - Advisory Committee on Black Appointments, 1972 (Folder 58.4)
  - Executive Committee — Black Affairs, 1972 Apr (Folder 58.5)
  - Urban Center for Black Studies, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.6)
  - Black Studies Appointments, 1971 (Folder 58.7)
  - Black Applicants for Positions, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.8)
  - Black Student Counselor — Jean O. Ramey, 1970-1972 (Folder 58.9)
  - Black Studies paper for Board of Trustees Meeting, 1972 May (Folder 58.10)
  - Committee to Review Services for Black Students, 1972 (Folder 58.11)
  - Black Students, 1972 (Folder 58.12)
  - Local Representatives from Black Community, 1972 (Folder 58.13)
  - Visiting Committee for Black Studies — Material Sent 11/14/72, 1970-1972 (Folder 58.14)
  - Black Studies Program — Visiting Committee, 1972 (Folder 58.15)
  - Black Affairs, 1971-1972 (Folder 58.16)
  - Black Affairs: Chronological File, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.17)
  - Black Affairs, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.18)
  - Sarah Gibson Blanding, 1971-1973 (Folder 58.19)
  - Central Administration, 1971-1972 (Folder 58.20)
  - Clippings, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.21)
  - Coeducation, 1973 (Folder 58.22)
  - Computer Center, 1969-1973 (Folder 58.23)
  - Diplomas to Male Students in previous years (GI Bill), 1972 (Folder 58.24)
  - Faculty and Course Evaluation, 1971-1972 (Folder 58.25)
  - Faculty: Hiring and Review, 1971 (Folder 58.26)
  - Faculty Housing — Eligibility List (work sheets), 1972-1973 (Folder 58.27)
  - Faculty Housing, 1972 (Folder 58.28)
  - Faculty Housing, 1972 (Folder 58.29)
  - Faculty Leave System, 1972 (Folder 58.30)
  - Faculty: Unionization of, 1971 (Folder 58.31)
  - Faculty Waivers, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.32)
  - Student Fees, 1971-1972 (Folder 58.33)
  - Form Letters, 1971-1972 (Folder 58.34)
  - Growth of the College, 1972 (Folder 58.35)
  - Growth of the College, 1972 (Folder 58.36)
  - U.S. India Women’s College Program, 1971-1972 (Folder 58.37)
  - The Misc, 1972 (Folder 58.38)
  - Multidisciplinary program in Science, Technology and Society, 1972-1973 (Folder 58.39)
  - Off Campus Studies, 1971 (Folder 58.40)
  - Oath of Allegiance, 1969 (Folder 58.41)
  - President’s Report — 1964-1970, 1971 (Folder 58.42)
  - President’s Report, 1971 Jan- 1972 Oct (Folder 58.43)
  - Office of Public Relations — Administrative Director, Mary Gilbert, 1971-1972 (Folder 59.1)
  - Public Relations — News Office, 1971-1973 (Folder 59.2)
  - Vassar Views, 1971-1974 (Folder 59.3)
  - Questionnaires, 1972 (Folder 59.4)
  - Recommendations, 1971-1972 (Folder 59.5)
  - Salary Scale, 1971-1973 (Folder 59.6)
  - Salary Data, 1971-1973 (Folder 59.7)
  - Salary Budget 1972-1973 — Working Paper, 1971-1972 (Folder 59.8)
  - Faculty Salary Budget 1972-1973 — Working Paper, 1971-1972 (Folder 59.9)
  - Faculty Salary Budget 1973-1974 — Working Papers, 1972-1973 (Folder 59.10)
  - Faculty Salary Budget 1973-1974 — Working Paper, 1972 (Folder 59.11)
  - Senior Staff, 1972-1973 (Folder 59.12)
  - Mr. Simpson’s Notes to Himself, 1971-1973 (Folder 59.13)
  - Students — Exchange and Transfer, 1971-1973 (Folder 59.14)
  - Student Government Association, 1971-1973 (Folder 59.15)
  - Judicial Board — Student Disciplinary Cases, 1972 (Folder 59.16)
  - Student Housing Problems, 1971 (Folder 59.17)
  - Student Unrest, 1969-1971 (Folder 59.18)
  - Summer Institute in Geology, 1970-1971 (Folder 59.19)
  - Summer Program — Continuing Education, 1972-1973 (Folder 59.20)
  - Teaching Fellowships in Women’s Studies, 1973 (Folder 59.21)
  - Women’s Studies, 1971-1972 (Folder 59.22)
  - Women’s Studies, Responses to President’s Letter, 1971 (Folder 59.23)
  - Study of Year Round Operation, 1973 (Folder 59.24)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1973 (Folder 59.25)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1975 (Folder 59.26)
  - Assistant to the President (Mr. Fahlund), 1973-1975 (Folder 59.27)
  - Asian Studies, 1973-1975 (Folder 59.28)
  - Assistant to the president for Black Affairs, 1973-1974 (Folder 59.29)
  - Position of Advisor or Assistant to the President for Black Affairs, 1974 (Folder 59.30)
  - Serge Paul-Emile, Director Educational Services, Student Relations, 1975 (Folder 59.31)
  - Black Applicants for Positions, 1974 (Folder 59.32)
  - Black Affairs, 1973-1974 (Folder 59.33)
  - Black housing — Kendrick, 1975 (Folder 59.34)
  - Kendrick, 1974 (Folder 59.35)
  - Kendrick House — extra copy of some of the papers, 1974 (Folder 59.36)
  - Black Housing — Kendrick House, 1974 (Folder 59.37)
  - Black Affairs, 1974-1975 (Folder 59.38)
  - Black Affairs — President Simpsons file and notes, 1973 (Folder 59.39)
  - Faculty Committee on Black Studies, 1973-1974 (Folder 59.40)
  - Black Studies Program — Visiting Committee, 1975 (Folder 59.41)
  - Urban Center for Black Studies, 1973-1975 (Folder 59.42)
  - Black Students, 1973 (Folder 59.43)
  - Local Representatives from Black Community, 1973 (Folder 59.44)
  - Sarah Gibson Blanding, 1973-1975 (Folder 59.45)
  - Changing American Culture, 1973-1975 (Folder 59.46)
  - Vassar Chronicle, 1974 (Folder 59.47)
  - Clippings, 1973-1975 (Folder 59.48)
  - College Convocation, 1975 (Folder 59.49)
  - Vandals and Vandal Worship, 1975 Apr (Folder 59.50)
  - College Council, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.1)
  - Computer Center, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.2)
  - Drugs on Campus, 1974 (Folder 60.3)
  - Entertainment at President’s House, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.4)
  - Faculty Chairs, 1972-1974 (Folder 60.5)
  - Faculty Housing, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.6)
  - Faculty-Student Ratio Background Papers — Financial Crisis, 1969-1971 (Folder 60.7)
  - Faculty Tenure File, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.8)
  - Faculty: Tenure, 1972-1973 (Folder 60.9)
  - Faculty Tenure File — Pertinent papers, 1972-1974 (Folder 60.10)
  - Faculty Tenure, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.11)
  - Faculty: Criteria for Promotion and Tenure — President’s Statement, 1970 Apr 27 (Folder 60.12)
  - Multidisciplinary Program in Science, Technology and Society, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.13)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.14)
  - President’s Meeting with Department Chairmen and FPCC, 1974 (Folder 60.15)
  - President’s Report, 1974 Dec (Folder 60.16)
  - Presidential Luncheons, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.17)
  - Office of Public Relations Administrative Director — Mary Gilbert, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.18)
  - Public Relations — News Office, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.19)
  - Vassar Views, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.20)
  - Vassar Views, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.21)
  - Publications, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.22)
  - Vassar Priorities, 1974 (Folder 60.23)
  - Registration — 1975, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.24)
  - Research Assistants employed on grants from NSF, Public Health Services, etc., 1973 (Folder 60.25)
  - Salary Scale, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.26)
  - Security Office Report, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.27)
  - Salary Data, 1974 (Folder 60.28)
  - Senior Staff, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.29)
  - Senior Staff, 1972-1975 (Folder 60.30)
  - Size of the College, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.31)
  - Student Government Association, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.32)
  - Senate — Thomas, 1974 (Folder 60.33)
  - Student Government Association, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.34)
  - Students — Exchange and Transfer, 1974-1975 (Folder 60.35)
  - Student Fees, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.36)
  - Vassar Chronicle, 1975 May (Folder 60.37)
  - The Misc, 1973-1974 (Folder 60.38)
  - Student Interns, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.39)
  - 1975 Yearbook (Folder 60.40)
  - Summer Program — Continuing Education, 1974 (Folder 60.41)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1974 (Folder 60.42)
  - Vassariana, 1973 (Folder 60.43)
  - Women’s Studies, 1973-1975 (Folder 60.44)
  - A — General, 1976-1978 (Folder 60.45)
  - Administrative Recess Schedules, 1974-1977 (Folder 60.46)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1975-1976 (Folder 60.47)
  - Administrative Staff Meetings, 1975-1977 (Folder 60.48)
  - Applicants — Administrative, 1974-1977 (Folder 60.49)
  - Applicants for Faculty Positions (General), 1970-1978 (Folder 60.50)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1976-1978 (Folder 60.51)
  - American Association of Presidents of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1977-1978 (Folder 60.52)
  - American Association of University Women, 1972-1977 (Folder 60.53)
  - American Association on Education (Correspondence), 1976-1978 (Folder 60.54)
  - American Council on Education (Newsletter — Higher Education and National Affairs), 1977-1978 (Folder 60.55)
  - American Association of University professors, 1975-1977 (Folder 60.56)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1975-1978 (Folder 60.57)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1975-1977 (Folder 60.58)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1975-1976 (Folder 60.59)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1976-1978 (Folder 61.1)
  - Association of Governing Boards, 1976-1977 (Folder 61.2)
  - Association of Governing Boards, 1975-1976 (Folder 61.3)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1971-1977 (Folder 61.4)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1974-1979 (Folder 61.5)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1977-1978 (Folder 61.6)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1975-1976 (Folder 61.7)
  - Council on Post-secondary Accreditation, 1977 Dec (Folder 61.8)
  - CBFSEI (Clearinghouse for Community Based Free Standing Educational Institutions), 1977 (Folder 61.9)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1972-1978 (Folder 61.10)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools (Comm. On Higher Education — Annual Institutional Data Summary), 1977 (Folder 61.11)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1976-1978 (Folder 61.12)
  - Auditor’s Report, 1975-1977 (Folder 61.13)
  - B — General Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Folder 61.14)
  - Black Affairs, 1977 (Folder 61.15)
  - Urban Center for Africana Studies, 1975-1978 (Folder 61.16)
  - C — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 61.17)
  - Clippings, 1975-1977 (Folder 61.18)
  - College Center, 1972-1978 (Folder 61.19)
  - Dean’s Lunch Discussions, 1977 Nov (Folder 61.20)
  - College Council, 1075-1977 (Folder 61.21)
  - Commencement, 1975 (Folder 61.22)
  - Commencement, 1976 (Folder 61.23)
  - Commencement, 1977 (Folder 61.24)
  - Commencement, 1978 (Folder 61.25)
  - Consultants, 1974-1978 (Folder 61.26)
  - Critical Language Program, 1976 (Folder 61.27)
  - D — General Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Folder 62.1)
  - Debate Society, 1978 (Folder 62.2)
  - E — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.3)
  - E-P-E 15-Minute Reports, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.4)
  - Experiment in international Living, 1974-1976 (Folder 62.5)
  - F — General Correspondence, 1977 (Folder 62.6)
  - Federal Legislation, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.7)
  - Founder’s Day, 1977 (Folder 62.8)
  - G — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.9)
  - Grant Information, 1977-1978 (Folder 62.10)
  - H — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.11)
  - HEOP, 1973-1977 (Folder 62.12)
  - Horticulturist, 1973-1978 (Folder 62.13)
  - Horticulturalist, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.14)
  - I — General Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Folder 62.15)
  - Inauguration, 1978 Apr (Folder 62.16)
  - Institute of International Education, 1972-1975 (Folder 62.17)
  - Invitations to the President, 1977 (Folder 62.18)
  - J — General Correspondence, 1976 (Folder 62.19)
  - K — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.20)
  - L — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.21)
  - Library Dedication Committee, 1975-1977 (Folder 62.22)
  - M — General, 1976-1978 (Folder 62.23)
  - Mathew Club, 1977 (Folder 62.24)
  - Mailing Lists, 1977 (Folder 62.25)
  - N — General Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Folder 62.26)
  - New York State Education Department (Hegis Reports), 1977-1978 (Folder 62.27)
  - New York State Education Department, 1975-1978 (Folder 62.28)
  - Notices — Official, 1977-1978 (Folder 62.29)
  - O — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.30)
  - P — General Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Folder 62.31)
  - Entertainment at President’s House, 1975-1977 (Folder 62.32)
  - President-Elect — Virginia B. Smith, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.33)
  - Presidential Evaluation, 1976 (Folder 62.34)
  - President’s Report, 1975-1976 (Folder 62.35)
  - President’s Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Folder 62.36)
  - Presidential Luncheons, 1975-1976 (Folder 62.37)
  - Presidential Search, 1974-1977; (2 folders) (Folder 62.38)
  - Proposals, 1976-1978 (Folder 62.39)
  - Questionnaires, 1975-1977 (Folder 62.40)
  - R — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.41)
  - S — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 62.42)
  - Search Committee Recommendations, 1975-1977 (Folder 62.43)
  - Security Reports, 1977-1978 (Folder 63.1)
  - Senior Staff Meetings, 1977-1978 (Folder 63.2)
  - Senior Staff Members’ Schedules, 1977-1978 (Folder 63.3)
  - Seven-College Conference, 1977 (Folder 63.4)
  - Seven-College Conference, 1976 (Folder 63.5)
  - Seven-College Conference, 1975 (Folder 63.6)
  - Size of the College, 1976 (Folder 63.7)
  - Soccer Trip, 1977-1978 (Folder 63.8)
  - Social Responsibility Seminar, 1977 (Folder 63.9)
  - Sunset Lake, 1976-1977 (Folder 63.10)
  - Class of 1978 (Folder 63.11)